(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-07T22:12:02.985748",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Checkmate, I'm a superstar
Stay insane, but you rock with it
Like 24/7 I'm a hot mess ya love-hate
Like 24/7 I'm a hot mess, love-hate
Get less boring, oh my god!!
ホームラン, バタバタ swing my shot
Homerun, fluttering, swing my shot
Like a villainous villainess, bring home the jackpot
勇者も悪役も変わらない
Heroes and villains are no different
派手にブチかまそう
Let's make a flashy splash
Life's just a tightrope, why not stop to fool around?
"Chaotic good" is peak right now
I can show ya how
Don't get confused, we are not the same
I'm a ruthless dame
"Good vs evil" is so overdone
Let's all kick back and party
Just leave it to moi
Loosen my lips
Loosen my li-li-lips
That's karma
Loosen my lips
I'm about to say some ish, get it
That's karma
Sorry I'm just better
Sorry we're go-getters
Ain't my fault we're wicked, stunning, tricky
Why you running?
Bet 'cha think you're clever
Whatever!
Talk about a "kumbaya"
欲望 召し上がれ
Feast upon your desires
アイ$ハート get down ウィンク
Eye-heart, get down, wink
See yonara サイコ ですわ
See ya, sayonara, you're psycho
ドメスティック
Domestic
ドラマティック
Dramatic
愛しき 人々
Beloved people
この指とまれ
Gather around this finger
ハイ になって 弾け て
Getting high and bursting
意気地なし さあ踊り踊れ
Cowards, come on, dance and dance
驚異的 正体 どしてちょうだい
Miraculous true identity, what's going on?
目醒めのパラダイス
Awakening paradise
焦がれ合う
Yearning for each other
感覚が 蛍明 蛍明
Senses glowing, glowing
フルボッコんボっ ちゃ って
Utterly beaten down and bruised
欲望 召し上がれ
Feast upon your desires
アイ$ハート get down ウィンク
Eye-heart, get down, wink
See yonara サイコ ですわ
See ya, sayonara, you're psycho
Loosen my lips
Loosen my li-li-lips
That's karma
Loosen my lips
I'm about to say some ish, get it
That's karma
ずぶずぶからずぶと
Sinking deeper and deeper
衝動から猛攻か
From impulse to fierce attack
ほらあっという間に一瞬で 人生はエンディングにさえ
Look, in the blink of an eye, life even reaches its ending
毒々しい本能
Venomous instincts
喰らえ咆哮
Devour the roar
Talk about a "kumbaya"
Sorry I'm just better
Sorry we're go-getters
Ain't my fault we're wicked, stunning, tricky
lined up, one by one
to play the soldiers of vain corporation
商談なら 1 on 1
Negotiation? 1 on 1
あした ら の 言い値 で 即決
Quick decisions at tomorrow's price
are you entertained now?
let the karma rain down
i can play pierrot if it means i'll be the last clown
living in the twisted diorama that is industry
fail, and we're in the streets
とびっきりを どうぞ ！
Enjoy the absolute best!
今夜 も 変身 君 ら 様々
Tonight too, transforming for you all
一緒に あした に 夢見 て よ freaker
Dreaming of tomorrow together, freaker
よそおう 平気 work hard , play harder
Acting nonchalant, work hard, play harder
君と だから 全部 let 's dig in
Since it's with you, let's dig all in
mirror , mirror tell me again
mirror, mirror tell me again
if it was fated that i made it , or a stroke of luck ?
if it was fated that i made it, or a stroke of luck?
louder , clearer
louder, clearer
just say that i 'm enough
just say that i'm enough
you lie so well
一撃 で 虚
An illusion in a single strike
テメェ の 所為 です
It's all your fucking fault
どの 子 が 好き ？
Which girl do you like?
この 子 に 決め た
Well, I've chosen this one.
角度 を 調節
Adjust the angle
覚悟 微 調整
Preparation, fine-tuning
飽きたらポイから捨て去る
Since you can toss her when you're tired
place any bets
decide who is special and discard the rest
gambler by nature
chips start to stack
racing lovely animals until they crack
や いの や いの
Aren't you persistent!
貼り付け parasite
You clingy parasite
ヤンデレッテレル テメェ の 所為 です
Going crazy, and it's your fault
black out , break down
black out, break down
toss it when you 've had enough
toss it when you've had enough
やっ て ちまえ いっ ちゃ え
Go, go, go on now!
i can tell you 're not impressed
i can tell you're not impressed
右向け右
Face to the right now
左 向け 左
Now to the left, left
leave the defective , unworthy of investment
leave the defective, unworthy of investment
hot mess , worthless doll
hot mess, worthless doll
gambler by nature
chips start to stack
racing lovely animals until they crack
beautiful dreams await modest hearts
close your eyes and all you 'll see is black
close your eyes and all you'll see is black
才能 サイコパス と 紙一重
There's a fine line between talented and psychopath
やっ ちまっ た の 後悔 で fever
A fever of regret from your actions
もういい ！
I've had enough!
starving !
I'm starving!
時間 の ムダ 空間
What a waste of time!
やっ て ちまえ いっ ちゃ え
Go, go, go on now!
i can tell you 're not impressed
i can tell you're not impressed
ウゼェ バカ アホ カス
Disgusting, stupid, idiot, trash
こち とら 最 下層
We are the lowest of the low
どうに かなり そう
I think I can manage
どうにでも なり そう
But it could go either way
ぶっ とい 絆
Strong ties, yet—
lonely lonely
trouble in paradise
oh , if only
oh, if only
愛 を 歌っ て 「 あいうえお 」 から 「 ん 」 まで 昇っ て
Singing of love, from 'aiueo' up to 'n'
見下し て やる わ
I'll look down at you
や いの や いの
Aren't you persistent!
貼り付け parasite
You clingy parasite
ヤンデレッテレル テメェ の 所為 です
Going crazy, and it's your fucking fault
black out , break down
black out, break down
toss it when you 're out of love
toss it when you're out of love
やっ て ちまえ いっ ちゃ え
Go, go, go on now!
i 'm the one that 's not impressed
i'm the one that's not impressed
テメェ の 所為 です
It's all your fucking fault!
責任 取り な はれ
Take responsibility
パッ と 光っ て 華 ひらく わ
With a flash of light, it'll be so beautiful
place any bets
decide who is special and discard the rest
gambler by nature
chips start to stack
racing lovely animals until they crack
や いの や いの
Aren't you persistent!
貼り付け parasite
You clingy parasite
ヤンデレッテレル テメェ の 所為 です
Going crazy, and it's your fault
black out , break down
black out, break down
toss it when you 've had enough
toss it when you've had enough
やっ て ちまえ いっ ちゃ え
Go, go, go on now!
i can tell you 're not impressed
i can tell you're not impressed
右向け右
Face to the right now
左 向け 左
Now to the left, left
leave the defective , unworthy of investment
leave the defective, unworthy of investment
hot mess , worthless doll
hot mess, worthless doll
gambler by nature
chips start to stack
racing lovely animals until they crack
beautiful dreams await modest hearts
close your eyes and all you 'll see is black
close your eyes and all you'll see is black
才能 サイコパス と 紙一重
There's a fine line between talented and psychopath
やっ ちまっ た の 後悔 で fever
A fever of regret from your actions
もういい ！
I've had enough!
starving !
I'm starving!
時間 の ムダ
What a waste of time!
やっ て ちまえ いっ ちゃ え i can tell you 're not impressed
Go, go, go on now! I can tell you're not impressed
ウゼェ バカ アホ カス
Disgusting, stupid, idiot, trash
こち とら 最 下層
We are the lowest of the low
どうに かなり そう
I think I can manage
どうにでも なり そう
But it could go either way
ぶっ とい 絆 lonely lonely
Strong ties, yet— lonely lonely
trouble in paradise
oh , if only
oh, if only
愛 を 歌っ て 「 あいうえお 」 から 「 ん 」 まで 昇っ て
Singing of love, from 'aiueo' up to 'n'
見下し て やる わ
I'll look down at you
や いの や いの 貼り付け parasite
Aren't you persistent, you clingy parasite!
ヤンデレッテレル テメェ の 所為 です
Going crazy, and it's your fucking fault
black out , break down
black out, break down
toss it when you 're out of love
toss it when you're out of love
i 'm the one that 's not impressed
i'm the one that's not impressed
皆さん Welcome, welcome to
Everyone, welcome, welcome to
a very special showing of several songs from my brand new album Phantomime.
As you can see, the stage that I'm performing on today is a bit different than the usual...
As you can see, the stage that I'm performing on today is a bit different than usual.
Um, but we wanted to make this kind of like, a more intimate feeling setting, I guess.
Um, we wanted to make this a more intimate feeling setting, I guess.
Um, and I know that you guys at home are watching, so I'm just kind of imagining the audience all around me.
And I know you guys at home are watching, so I'm imagining the audience all around me.
It kind of feels like a like a TV live, to be honest. It's really cool.
It kind of feels like a TV live, to be honest. It's really cool.
Just now I performed two songs that I've already done before off of the album... two songs that you guys are very familiar with, of course,
Just now I performed two songs off of the album you're very familiar with, of course,
Gogetters...
Gogetters from Suisei...
excited about, but I won't spoil the surprise.
So with that being said,
let's go, check it out.
Cult Following.
cut your other ties
this ain't the only battlefield I can televise
ego is enormous, so put the camera down and face it
they went and got complacent
come and run with me
you say you stand for nothing, no one else can relate
just know the company you keep is in the business of hate
are you afraid?
don't run away, I'm close to getting paid
i'll be dancing on my own in a bulletproof vest
go and shoot, shoot, shoot, aww, baby, did you miss?
ricochet, ricochet
you can think about me any time, of any day
forget your street fights
this a trench war
i'll make you march, march, march till you hit the floor
getting thirsty for collision
let them wonder what they're missing in the front row
now here we go
this ain't a lifeline
it's a call-to-arms
become the risen, the unforgiven, make a decision
if you're looking for permission to riot, you got it wrong
say goodbye to your identity, click, flash, now you belong
the situation isn't fluid at all, took out my reddest paints and markers and i ruined the wall
it's not that complicated, i could choose to run, but i crawl to slit the ankles of the skeptics who are wishing we fall
i'll be dancing on my own in a bulletproof vest
go and shoot, shoot, shoot, aww, baby, did you miss?
ricochet, ricochet
you can think about me any time, of any day
forget your street fights
this a trench war
i'll make you march, march, march till you hit the floor
getting thirsty for collision
let them wonder what they're missing in the front row
now here we go
this ain't a lifeline
it's a call-to-arms
become the risen, the unforgiven, make a decision
if you're looking for permission to riot, you got it wrong
say goodbye to your identity, click, flash, now you belong
i'll be dancing on my own in a bulletproof vest, they can shoot, shoot, shoot, and we'll see who shoots best
fighting all our battles, know the kind too well, they go "ready, set, rage" then they follow us to hell
finger on the trigger, bout to cock it and run, got a lyric in the chamber but i'm aiming my own gun
forget your street fights
this a trench war
i'll make you march, march, march till you hit the floor
getting thirsty for collision
let them wonder what they're missing in the front row
now here we go
this ain't a lifeline
it's a call-to-arms
become the risen, the unforgiven, make a decision
if you're looking for permission to riot, you got it wrong
say goodbye to your identity, click, flash, now you belong
let them riot onward, lock and load
stand for nothing, play the coward, stand by someone, you're devoured, it's a sick and twisted miscreant's existence
hello again, my hideous foe
the tide is high, but i'm still low
you raise that gun like you're aiming for me, babe
cut and run, we can never be free, yeah
there is never any goal
a hide and seek, take a peek at the skill no one can teach
a dance with ideals that you know you'll never reach, picking a random "want to be" to be "somebody"
telephoned facts and poisoned wells, ready or not now, boys and girls?
high up on your throne, riding steady through the glow
hello again, my hideous foe
the tide is high, but i'm still low
you raise that gun like you're aiming for me, babe
cut and run, we can never be free, yeah
there is never any goal
a hide and seek
take a peek at the skill no one can teach
a dance with ideals that you know you'll never reach
picking a random "want to be" to be "somebody"
telephoned facts and poisoned wells
ready or not now, boys and girls?
high up on your throne
riding steady through the glow
perfect sinners made of gold
people come and go
only way that you can grow
is not to give a damn at all
feel the drive
when hell's breaking loose, come and dance with me
fever dies
i am what i am and they're out of my league
can't catch up, but we're still in the fight
may never take the leap but i tell myself "don't mind"
'cause i'm betting all on me
still here burning with desire
don't you tell me that you're tired
are ya joking? maybe choking while they're stoking up the fire
people say "you've lost your vision"
but you're seeing crystal clear
i'm making my own decisions before they let me disappear
what do you want from me? guessing we'll never agree
believing everybody ends up drowning in their own damn entropy
インターネット 亡者 you're addicted like i told ya
Internet ghouls, you're addicted like I told ya.
から回って 空になって そう さ みんな 燃えて こうや
Spinning out, turning empty, yes, everyone, burn on up.
people come and go
only way that you can grow
is not to give a damn at all
feel the drive
when hell's breaking loose, come and dance with me
fever dies
i am what i am and they're out of my league
can't catch up, but we're still in the fight
may never take the leap but i tell myself "don't mind"
'cause i'm betting all on me
キメまくった 妄想 後にひけない 焦燥
Hyped-up delusions, anxiety you can't back down from.
まきちらして わめきだして あたりちらし 暴走
Spreading it, shouting it, thrashing about out of control.
何番煎じなのか わかんねーな持論
How many times brewed is this theory of yours?
後生大事にドヤ顔で かましてる愚どん
Acting smug and cherishing it like a fool.
笑わせんな 効かせんな 君のその agenda
Don't make me laugh, don't play me with your agenda.
let it be known 消えろよ i will never surrender
Let it be known, disappear, I will never surrender.
people come and go there are highs and endless lows
only way that you can grow is not to give a damn at all
hello again, my hideous foe
the tide is high, but i'm not alone
feel the drive
when hell's breaking loose, come and dance with me
fever dies
i am what i am and they're out of my league
can't catch up, but we're still in the fight
may never take the leap but i tell myself "don't mind"
'cause i'm betting all on me
(don't mind, 'cause i'm betting all on me, yeah)
feel the drive
when hell's breaking loose, come and dance with me
fever dies
i am what i am and they're out of my league
can't catch up, but we're still in the fight
may never take the leap but i tell myself "don't mind"
'cause i'm betting all on me
feel the drive
when hell's breaking loose, come and dance with me
fever dies
i am what i am and they're out of my league
can't catch up, but we're still in the fight
may never take the leap but i tell myself "don't mind"
Thank you very much, everybody! That was
"DONMAI", my collaboration song with Jean-Ken Johnny of MAN WITH A MISSION.
Probably one of my favorite songs that I've ever made.
I seriously, I can't stop kind of listening to it on my own because I'm really, really proud of how it turned out,
I seriously—I can't stop listening to it on my own because I'm really, really proud of how it turned out.
and I feel like I got to use, um, I guess, a certain sort of like tone and sound of my vocals that I don't use very often,
And I feel like I got to use, um, I guess, a certain sort of tone and sound of my vocals that I don't use very often,
but I actually am like really happy with how it sounds,
but I'm actually really happy with how it sounds.
and I hope that you guys also enjoyed it lots and
And I hope that you guys also enjoyed it a lot, and
um, I feel like it's a song that I can show to my family, I might even show it to my sister, which is crazy
because she's like hyper normal person, I don't know, I think also my dad might really like this song,
because she's like a hyper-normal person, I don't know. I think also my dad might really like this song,
maybe, but most of all, I hope you guys enjoyed it,
as I'm really quite proud of it.
And so yeah, those were two songs that I haven't performed before, you guys!
Oh my gosh! Hatsuhiro desu! Deshita!
Oh my gosh! Hatsuhirodeshita!
It's like the first time, the first time that it was shown anywhere is Hatsuhiori,
so I hope that you guys enjoyed those two songs, but since the vibes are really good right now,
and I think you guys are enjoying the show, um, let's go ahead and do one more song
that you guys haven't heard me perform before.
The next song is called "Skeletons", produced by Yaffle.
It's, uh, it's another one of those songs that I feel like you guys were kind of asking for
a little bit more of like a, a softer, more emotional piece...
a little bit more of a softer, more emotional piece...
hold on, just let it go
shatter it all
time to decide
veiled skeleton
save and reload
time to decide
i am running low on time
it's all too broken inside to decide
hold on
just letting it go
or shatter it all
time to decide
veiled 透ける と
Veiled, translucent...
save and reload
time to decide
i'm running low on time
it's all too broken inside to decide
hold on
just letting it go
or shatter it all
time to decide
tied up 透ける 頃
Tied up, translucent...
save and reload
time to decide
i'm running low on time
it's all too broken inside to decide
it's outta my control
we'll just stay on the down-low
with no direction to grow
for the seed of a dream that expanded and landed me high, too high
there's gotta be something i missed while on the ride
we're all just drifting
let me go, let me go
i'm in the in-between, 亡霊 と swallow
I'm in the in-between, spirits to swallow
wait ! 龍 骸 香 stay in your lane 延滞 in the road
Wait! Stay in your lane, delayed in the road
my bad under the この 狂っ た うつし 世 なら
My bad under this crazy, illusory world
position ばっか 気 に し ちあっ て ん の i'm not greed
Care too much about position, I'm not greedy
and people ask “ why your ass still a hot mess ? ”
And people ask, "Why your ass still a hot mess?"
like they don't figure that improvement's a process
you lose some , you talk less , you work on your aim
You lose some, you talk less, you work on your aim
and spare the others that ' ll follow any meaningless shame
And spare the others that'll follow any meaningless shame
at times i cannot see the point of me being here
well i 'll reminisce about it all in a couple of years
Well, I'll reminisce about it all in a couple of years
the age of “ misfit ”
The age of "misfit"
optimistic that i missed it
until i flash back to every wall that my fist hit
at my limit , when i 'm quick to give up the fight
At my limit, when I'm quick to give up the fight
miracles gather in the mundane , and they catch the light
Miracles gather in the mundane, and they catch the light
i notice 蓬莱 jump で 飛び越え ちまえ
I notice Hourai, jump and leap right over it
吐い て 捨てる よう な 日 が ある と も
Even if there are days you just want to throw it all away
it's out of our control
let's just stay on the down-low
with no direction to grow
for the seed of a dream that expanded and landed me high, too high
there's gotta be something we missed on the ride
if this is only the beginning of the fiction we read over and over
like a fairytale that doesn't leave your head
i 'll make believe that happily ever after waits at the end
I'll make believe that happily ever after waits at the end
while just imagining the stories i would rather live instead
can't fix all the cracks like a 死んだ skeletons
Can't fix all the cracks like dead skeletons
手 を 伸ばせ
Reach out your hands
この 目 で
With your own eyes
見届ける
Witness it through
まだ ここ に は 誰 も 居 ない
No one is here yet
あたし の こと は 何 も 気 に しない で
Don't worry about a thing regarding me
この 痛み の 姿 形 で さえ も
Even in the shape and form of this pain
じき に 正しい 方 へ 進ん で いっ て
Advancing steadily toward the right path
それ が 光 の よう に 視 える 手 筈 だ
Arranged so it looks like a guiding light
we're all just drifting
let me go, let me go
Thank you. That was "Skeletons", my collaboration song with Yaffle-san.
I hope that you guys enjoyed the show today, but...
um, as all wonderful plays must come to an end,
so must this live. But wherever you are in your life, um, as an actor or player in the grand play that is existence,
I hope you're doing well, and I hope that these songs provide some kind of happiness for you, um, in your time of need, whatever that time might be, I guess.
I hope that you'll listen to "Phantomime", hontoni, eto, kiite kudasai, hontoni kiite hoshii, eto, "Phantomime", shin-album desu.
I hope that you'll listen to "Phantomime"—seriously, please listen to it. Really want you to listen to it. It's "Phantomime", my new album.
Eto, majide imamade ichiban saikou no sakuhin ni narimashita. Check shite kudasai!
Honestly, it's turned out to be my best work ever. Please check it out!
I'd really love it if you could listen to it lots, um, and share it, help me share it with the world.
Help me share with the world my best piece until now. Thank you so much everyone.
Peace!